http://www.absorption.com/privacy-statement/

New eBook Release: Potency Assay Guide for Cell & Gene Therapy Products
Learn More
x
ServicesBy Molecule/Product TypeSMALL MOLECULE SERVICESBioanalytical Testing ServicesBioequivalence Testing (BCS, IVRT/IVPT)Drug Transporter Testing ServicesIn Vitro Dissolution Absorption System (IDAS)Metabolism Testing ServicesPermeability Testing ServicesPhysicochemical Properties/Dose SelectionPreclinical PK Testing ServicesPreclinical Toxicology Testing ServicesBIOLOGICS & GENE THERAPYAnalyticalBioanalytical Testing ServicesBiodistribution & SheddingIn VivoPotency Assay DevelopmentPreclinical PK Testing ServicesPreclinical Toxicology Testing ServicesMEDICAL DEVICE IN VIVOCardiovascular TestingMetabolic DiseasesOrthopedic Device TestingSurgical Models for Ocular and Cardiovascular DiseasesBY APPLICATION AREABIOANALYTICAL TESTINGCARDIOVASCULAR TESTINGDERMAL TESTINGIn Vitro Release Testing (IVRT)In Vitro Permeation Testing (IVPT)OCULAR TESTINGCell and Gene TherapyEx Vivo PermeabilityIn Vivo CapabilitiesVascular Disease and Surgical ModelsPRECLINICAL PK SERVICESTOXICOLOGY TESTING SERVICESBY STUDY TYPEIN VITROIN VIVOWhat Are You Looking For?
Products search
E-StoreIn Vitro ServicesPermeability AssaysCell Based AssaysIVPT ServicesMetabolismCYP Inhibition AssessmentCYP Substrate AssessmentMetabolic StabilityMetabolite Identification Using HRMSUGT InteractionsTransportersInhibition – Single ConcentrationInhibition – IC50Substrate AssessmentPhysicochemical PropertiesLogD / SolubilityProtein BindingBlood to Plasma RatioMatrix StabilityIn Vivo ServicesPharmacokineticsMore ServicesAssay Ready PlatesClinical PathologyWhat Are You Looking For?
Products search
Knowledge CenterAbsorbThis BlogCASE STUDIESPRESENTATIONSPUBLICATIONSSCIENTIFIC POSTERSWEBINARSFAQsPRECLINICAL 101CompanyTHE ABSORPTION DIFFERENCEMANAGEMENT TEAMPRESS RELEASESCAREERSContact
Home > Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
We respect the privacy of the visitors to our website.
This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information you submit to us through our website.
“Personal Information” is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and other information that is not otherwise publicly available.
User Consent
By submitting Personal Information through our website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Collection of Personal Information
We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our website. The information we collect are:
For visitors who leave their contact information:
First and Last Name
Email Address
Business or Institution
Postal/Zip
Country
Message (optional)
For visitors who email us:
First and Last Name
Email Address
Any content included in the email.
For all visitors
As you navigate our website, certain passive information will also be collected, including Internet Protocol addresses, cookies and navigational data. This type of information will be used for the purposes of gathering data to provide improved administration of our website, and to improve the quality of your experience when interacting with our website.
Use of Personal Information
In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We do not share your Personal Information with third parties.
If we are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Regarding Children
Our website is not designed for children under the age of 15. We will not deliberately gather Personal Information about visitors in this age group, and do not collect any information on this website with respect to age.
Links to Other Sites
Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside websites.
Opting out of Communications
In every email we send, we provide instructions regarding how to opt-out of receiving future mailings. You may also opt-out of receiving future mailings by email marketing@absorption.com to unsubscribe.
Data Security
We use industry-standard methods to secure the communication of Personal Information from your computer to our servers. In addition, we use industry-standard methods of securing our databases of Personal Information, including the use of firewalls. Except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we limit access to Personal Information databases to those persons in our organization who have a business need for such access. However, you should know that no company, including Rigel, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. We are in compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  For any questions regarding your personal information, please email us at contact@absorption.com.
Contact Us
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us: Absorption Systems LLC
436 Creamery Way, Suite 600
Exton, PA 19341
contact@absorption.com
Privacy Policy Updates
This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and any changes will be posted on this site. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our website. Continued use of our website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. This policy was last updated on January 1, 2020.
×
Generic selectors
Exact matches only
Exact matches only
Search in title
Search in title
Search in content
Search in content
Bioequivalence Testing (BCS, IVRT/IVPT)
Drug Transporter Testing Services
In Vitro Dissolution Absorption System (IDAS)
In Vitro Release Testing (IVRT)
In Vitro Permeation Testing (IVPT)
What Are You Looking For?
What Are You Looking For?
